precisesecurity.com 2014-11-22

# Privacy Policy - precisesecurity.com

### Privacy Policy Statement

This is the web site of PreciseSecurity.

For each visitor to our web page, our Web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address. Information you may provide through comments, discussions are voluntary acts, and we will not be held responsible if it was collected and used by third parties. This is beyond our control.

### Personal Information

We collect the personal information of those who post messages to our discussion area, and e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail. The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded. We will not use your information for other activities particularly without your voluntary approval.

### Disclosure to Third Parties

In some circumstances, when you obtain legitimate software from this web site, our affiliate counterpart may collect necessary information to complete the registration process. We can guarantee that those data are solely used for business transaction purpose only. Any information collected from you will not be sold, rented or disclosed in any way.

Precisesecurity.com may also provide links to other reputable web sites as useful references. Be aware that these third party web sites also have their own privacy policy. We are not responsible for information and data collected by third party web sites you may visit as referred by us.

### Cookies and Advertisements

We use third party advertising campaign to support the operation of this web site. As of this latest policy update (March 21, 2012), we are serving Google Adsense advertisements. Apart from that, we also offers anti-malware product such as MalwareBytes Anti-Malware and SuperAntiSpyware.

With respect to advertisements, we try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with companies that we allow to promote their products on this web site. As a result of your visit to our site, third party advertisers may set Internet cookies and collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and click-stream information. We have no jurisdiction over cookies implemented by third parties, as such, it is not covered in this Privacy Policy. You may view individual advertisers privacy policy below.

  * **Google Policies and Principles** – <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>
  * **MalwareBytes Anti-Malware Privacy Policy** – <http://www.malwarebytes.org/privacy_policy>
  * **SuperAntiSPyware Privacy Policy** – <http://www.superantispyware.com/privacy_policy.html>

### Security

With respect to security: We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. All data are stored on secured data facilities.

### Enforcement

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, or if feel that there are information needed to get remove from this web site, you may reach us by filling this [form](http://www.precisesecurity.com/contact/).
